[{"answer": "Where's my friend", "docId": "solaris_script.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " He'll let me in", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Gibarian warned me.  He left me a message", "docId": "solaris_script.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "She was real.  Where did she come from", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "What are they", "docId": "solaris_script.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "To calm my anxiety", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Probably", "docId": "solaris_script.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Told you what", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "And I just want to know if I'm crazy or not", "docId": "solaris_script.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You go home", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "You're better when you take them", "docId": "solaris_script.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "All right.  How about I feel better when you take them", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What do you remember", "docId": "solaris_script.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Do you remember my friend?  The Beatles?  Movies, books, restaurants, friends", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "But what if Solaris is what there was before The Big Bang", "docId": "solaris_script.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "As I said, then it's God, right", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Stop equivocating!  Unbelievable, how you equivocate!  You, the atheist, you're more dogmatic than any holy person I've ever seen! This is happening, my friend.  Wake up", "docId": "solaris_script.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Who are you trying to convince", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Yes.  Especially toward the end", "docId": "solaris_script.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You... she said I didn't love her", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Was she right", "docId": "solaris_script.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " I love you, too", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What's wrong", "docId": "solaris_script.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You said he was dead", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Gibarian.  He was here", "docId": "solaris_script.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "He is.  But he was here..", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Neither did I", "docId": "solaris_script.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I never said I didn't", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I can't stay here", "docId": "solaris_script.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Then you won't make it", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "That's impossible.  I'm not my friend", "docId": "solaris_script.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I... I am my friend.  But I am not the woman you loved ten years ago", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Who are you, then", "docId": "solaris_script.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Yes, you are", "qsentId": 34}]